So, remember, I have all this brain up here, just floating.
The brain,
but you can have different types of tensions that can manifest.
And they will register at the level of the eyes, you see.
This is where we can try to rebalance them a bit more quickly,
a process of ascensus, you see.
I may look like this, but I have all my memory right here.
And where does it express itself? It expresses itself in my zone B.
That was an ascensus, now it's a descensus, you see.
With a posterior repositioning,
people who have very sunken eyeballs like that,
and who present like this, depressive, somewhat.
Or who are like this.
Poor left-right connection.
Here, you have significant torsions.
Here, you have these dissociations.
It also has an impact, like this.
You see, with the different positions of the global brain.
But the eyes express themselves in this state,
they are the expression of this position.
Then we have the relationship with the development of the skull now.
So here we saw the eye with the development of the brain,
now we will see the eye with the development of the skull.